

Full Stack Web Dev

Sr. Technical Support Engineer

Skills - Experience

- Mac & Win OS, iOS
- Microsoft Office
- GitHub
- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript, jQuery & React.js
- Node.js
- Bootstrap
- MySQL & MongoDB
- Express.js
- PostMan & GraphQL
- REST API
- Splunk & DataDog

Certifications

- Salesforce Administrator
- Salesforce Advanced Admin
- Salesforce Platform App Builder
- Full Stack Web Development

Education

- Bachelor's in Science of Information Technology
- Associate in Science of Medical Assisting

Maribel Ellison

903-812-2300

maribel.duron86@gmail.com

LinkedIn

<u>GitHub</u>

Portfolio

Profile Summary

I have made and continue to make customer support and happiness my number one goal. I have proven that throughout my 10+ years of experience as a customer facing Technical Support Engineer. In addition to that, I have experience working on SaaS platforms such as Salesforce.com, Zendesk, and HubSpot. During that time I also earned my BSIT in June 2015 and my Full Stack Web Development Certification from the University of Arizona Coding Bootcamp in June 2021. I hope to join a company that will allow me to grow and learn with them while keeping customers as my first priority.

Work Experience

Salesforce, Inc. March 2022 - Sept. 2023 Senior Technical Account Manager (TAM)

- Manage multiple Signature Accounts concurrently to ensure they are receiving and taking advantage of their entitled Signature offerings
- Drive cases towards resolution by following up with Support, Engineers, Product Managers, and escalating to management as necessary
- Present weekly/biweekly/monthly organization health to include tracking customer projects and priorities
- Give insight into instance limits being reached/exceeded, long running processes, errors during process execution
- Present all major release information that is relevant to the org, to include technology that will be retired/sunsetted, and functionality that will be automatically enabled
- Work through the business cycle from development thru Go-Live and stabilization to ensure that the correct individuals are working with the customer if issues arise and that monitoring is occurring during deployments and Go-Lives

Parsable Inc, March 2021 - March 2022 Senior Support Specialist

- Track tickets in Zendesk and work with customers on functionality/issues with specified products
- Debug issues using web dev console, Parsable mobile logs, AWS logs via DataDog, Amplitude logs, and PostMan queries
- Work with engineers to resolve defects in product code by replicating/ pinpointing issue layer/location
- Work with the Customer Support Managers (CSMs) to track, update, and push existing tickets
- Worked on call hours to troubleshoot system down issues to resolution
- Assisted with/owned LATAM tickets as the only Spanish speaking support agent
- Used Jira to create, update, and monitor enhancements, bugs, tasks, and internal feature requests
- Updated/approved internal knowledge documents in Confluence and updated jQuery and CSS in the Help Center to update UI/UX functionality

Zinier Inc., April 2020 - November 2020 Technical Support Lead, LATAM (T3)

- Track tickets in Zendesk while working with customers on specified products
- Subject Matter Expert (SME) for the Zinier mobile application

Maribel Ellison

Contact Me:

903-812-2300 maribel.duron86@gmail.com

Social:

LinkedIn GitHub Portfolio

Zinier Inc.

- Troubleshoot by reviewing JSON modules/workflows, running PostMan scripts, use web dev console, Zinier platform logs, AWS logs via DataDog, API logs, and mobile logs
- Host screen shares to walk clients through resolutions
- Work with engineers to resolve defects in product code by replicating/pinpointing issue layer/location and translate code into Spanish
- Work with the Customer Support Managers (CSMs) to track, update, and push existing tickets
- Assisted with/owned LATAM tickets as one the only LATAM support agents
- Used Jira to create, update, and monitor enhancements, bugs, tasks, and internal feature requests
- · Create, updated, and approved Knowledge documents in Confluence

ServiceMax Inc., April 20, 2015 - April 2020 Senior Support Manager (April 2019 - April 2020)

- Manage the Americas Critical Customer Support team (T3) by hosting weekly 1:1 to review metrics, provide mentoring, and report on and record technician metrics
- POC for client/account manager escalations and consult with the customer on best practices for customizations/implementations.
- Head customization projects to ensure that the correct architect is assigned to the correct project
- Debug issues using Salesforce's debug logs, web dev console, and mobile logs
- Create cases and work with salesforce technical support to provide timely case resolutions
- Attend customer on-sites to assist with account retention by addressing any and all customer open cases and additional issues
- Article creation for the ServiceMax Support Handbook

Regional Support Manager (March 2018 - April 2019)

- Manage a team of five US West Technical Support Engineers by hosting weekly 1:1 to review metrics and provide mentoring
- POC for client/account manager escalations as well as client hyper-care during and after major releases to ensure little, to no downtime
- Train Team Leads, Regional Managers, and provide coverage during alternating shifts or when regional managers are OOO.

Customer Support Team Lead (February 2017 - March 2018)

- Manage a team of five US West Technical Support Engineers by hosting weekly 1:1 to review metrics and provide mentoring
- Report on and record technician metrics to ensure that technicians exceed standards
- Conduct interviews for prospective candidates and onboard/train new technical support engineers
- Create a channel of communication between the Customer Account Managers and the Regional Team Leads in order to provide the best customer support experience

Technical Support Engineer (April 20, 2015 - February 2017)

- Track tickets in Salesforce to annotate client troubleshooting via email, phone, and screen share
- Debug client issues using Salesforce's debug logs, developer console, and mobile logs
- Assist in HTML changes for client output documents
- Work with the engineers to resolve defects found product code
- Create product solutions within Salesforce and ServiceMax managed package to assist other agents and customers with troubleshooting steps for specific issues
- Create test environments to replicate customer issues or test solutions

Sunquest Information Systems, Sept. 9, 2013 – April 17, 2015 Technical/Customer Service Support Specialist

 Track tickets in Salesforce for the Clinical Financial and Commercial Laboratory Sunquest products

Maribel Ellison

Contact Me:

903-812-2300 maribel.duron86@gmail.com

Social:

LinkedIn GitHub Portfolio

Sunquest Information Systems

- Work with customers to verify functionality or product issues while meeting the 90 minute SLA
- Work with the engineers to resolve bugs found in the Mumps product code
- Implemented the Salesforce Console and Knowledge in order to create product solutions within Salesforce
- Prepared and presented educational client offerings during the company kick-off
- Attended Salesforce's DreamForce 2014 event to assist with gathering information for future Salesforce implementations and created a Salesforce Customer Community template

Stream Global Services, Jan. 23, 2012 – May 23, 2013 Technical/Customer Service Support Professional (SF CRM Contract)

- Track tickets in Salesforce for configuration or product issues
- Assisted with the Summer '12 and Winter '13 releases
- Coach and mentor new employees
- Use screen shares to assist customers to resolution of issues/inquiries
- One of two bilingual technical support agents at my location

References available upon request